Guide to the A. Poulin Papers and BOA Editions Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- July 1988 Acquisition, 1956-1986; 1; 44.33; (39 boxes)
  - Audiovisual Material
    - Reel-to-reel Tapes
      - "A. Poulin, D. Sherwood, J. Logan" (2 of 3 reels), undated; 1; 1 7/8 speed (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397076)
      - "A. Poulin, D. Sherwood, J. Logan" (3 of 3 reels), undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397084)
      - "John Logan", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397092)
      - "T. S. Eliot, The Waste Land", undated; 1; Speed: 3 3/4 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397118)
      - "T. S. Eliot, The Four Quartets", undated; 1; Speed: 3 1/2 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397100)
      - "Reel #1: Paul Chapman and Father Cantius, undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397126)
      - "Reel #2: Protestant Cath. Dialogue", panel discussions, undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397134)
      - "Reel #4: Father Honan (all) and Ed Gargan (beginning)", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397142)
      - "Reel #5: Ed Gargan (conclusion) and Mon. Eve Panel (1st part)", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397217)
      - "Reel #6: Christianity & History Panel", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397209)
      - "Reel #7: John Logan", undated; 1; 7 1/2, 3 3/4 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397191)
      - "Reel #8: Modern Xian Lit Panel", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397159)
      - "Reel #9", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397167)
      - "Reel #11: The Christian in Society, Walsh, Thorman", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397175)
      - "Reel # 12: Thorman (2), Panel", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397183)
      - "Claude Gauthier: 1. Marie Noël, 2. Christmas Tree", 1976 August 25; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397381)
      - "Cohen New York?", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397050)
      - "Fr. Cansius Matura", 1962 November 23; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397399)
      - "The Writers Workshop w/ Galway Kinnell" (1 of 2 reels), 1971 November 5; 1; 7 1/2 ips; 75 minutes (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397357)
      - "The Writers Workshop w/ Galway Kinnell" (2 of 2 reels), 1971 November 5; 1; 3 3/4 ips (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397365)
      - "Dr. Hodgekinson", 1967 February 13; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397340)
        Recording time: 11:55; 7 1/2 speed, dual track
      - "Background music for 'For the Time Being'", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397332)
      - "Sides I & II - Claude Gauthier, interviewed by Al Poulin in French. Side II - after Gauthier, interview with Msgr. Prosper Durand", 1962 November 24; 1; Monophonic, speed at 7 1/2 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397266)
      - "Creative Writing Series: A. Poulin, Jr.", 1970 October 26; 1; 3 1/2 IPS (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397258)
        There is a list of contents included with this audiotape reel. They are included below.
        Creative Writing Series
        1. Quotes from Mark Twain
        2. Santora - New Poems
        3. Professor Poems
        3a. Fear Survey Poems
        3b. Movie Poems
        4. Angelic Poems
        5. Fish
        6. Paratrooper
        7. Bombadair
        8. This - Tomorrow - Today Poems
        9. Flute Making
        10. On His Unborn Child
        11. Script Prospective
        12. Front Parlor
        13. To My Brother
        14. The Dream
      - "Kenneth Koch Interview, David Shapiro, England", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397241)
      - "Robert Bly Reading of Poetry", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397233)
      - "Al Poulin Reading His Own Poetry, Clarke College, Dubuque, Iowa", 1970 February 19; 1; Track 1, 3 3/4 speed (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397225)
      - "706 - A. Poulin, Jr. CWS, 14. My Dream - Part II, 15. In Advent", 1970 October 26; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397324)
      - "Poulin and David DeTurk", radio program, 1st master, undated; 1; mono (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397316)
      - "SFC Presents: Development Program, Father Clarence, Father Donald, Father Frederick, [Jim?] Wells" / "Town + Gown", 1962 December 14; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397274)
      - "Saint Francis Promo Tape", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397308)
      - "Love. Saint Francis Presents" symposium, March 23; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397373)
        9 min. 37 secs.
      - "Saint Francis Presents Symposium", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397290)
      - "Saint Francis College Presents", undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397282)
      - MaGill Concert student interviews, undated; 1 (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397407)
        Contents of this audiotape reel are listed below.
        Side I / Side II
        Jo Berman
        Anna and Kate McGarigle
        Roger Missenbaum
        Ralph Rossman
      - "Claude Gauthier", undated; 1; 7 1/2 speed (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397415)
        A list of this audiotape reel's contents are listed below. Narration by Mr. Hoffman.
        Schoenberg: Fourth Movement, "Sonnet of Petrarca" from Serenade, op. 24
        Schoenberg: Canon" "The Parting of the Ways", op. 28 #1
        Varese: Poem Electronique
    - Audiocassettes
      Boxes 38-39: Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Anderson, Jon, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397449)
      - Ashbery, John (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1972 November 27; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397456)
      - Ashbery, John (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1972 November 27; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397464)
      - Bly, Robert, #2, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397472)
      - Creeley, Robert, Brockport Writers Forum, #2, 1973 April 2; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397480)
        57:40
      - Dickey reading (1 of 2 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397498)
      - Dickey interview (2 of 2 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397506)
      - Engle, Paul (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1973 January 22; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397514)
      - Engle, Paul (2 of 2 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397522)
      - Everson interview, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397530)
      - Ferlinghetti reading (1 of 3 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397548)
      - Ferlinghetti reading, tape 2 (2 of 3 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397563)
      - Ferlinghetti interview (3 of 3 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397555)
      - Ginsberg (1 of 2 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397571)
      - Ginsberg (2 of 2 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397589)
      - Hayden, Robert, Writers Forum (1 of 2 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397597)
        Runtime: 59:20
      - Hayden, Robert (2 of 2 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397605)
      - Hoffman, Daniel, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397613)
      - Hugo, Richard (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1974 October 16; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397621)
      - Hugo, Richard reading "Letter to John Logan" (2 of 2 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397639)
      - Ignatow, David, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397654)
      - Jong, Erica, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397647)
      - Kunitz, Stanley, 1974 December 12; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397662)
      - Levertov, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397670)
      - Logan, Writers Forum, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397688)
        Running time: 30 minutes.
      - Malanga, Gerard, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397696)
      - Matthews, William, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397704)
      - Plumly, Stanley, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397712)
      - Poulin, Al, University of Athens (1 of 3 audiocassettes), 1980; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397720)
      - Poulin, Al readings (2 of 3 audiocassettes), 1974 February 9; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397738)
      - Poulin, Al, poems in Greek (3 of 3 audiocassettes), 1981 November 23; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397746)
        A list of contents is included below.
        Side 1 / Side 2
        The Widow's Taboo
        Figures in a Stranger's Dream
        The Nameless Garden
        Takis' poems in Greek
      - Reed, Ishmael, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397753)
      - Rich, Andrienne, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397761)
      - Rothenberg, undated; 1 (Box 38, Item barcode 39002091397779)
      - Sexton interview, undated; 1 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002091398991)
      - Simpson, Louis, 1974 April 3; 1 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002091399007)
      - Snodgrass, 1975 March 20; 1 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002091399015)
      - Snyder, Gary, undated; 1 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002091399023)
      - Strand, Mark interview, undated; 1 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002091399031)
      - Schaeffer, Susan Fromberg, undated; 1 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002091399049)
      - Tate, James, undated (Box 39, Item barcode 39002091399056)
      - Wilbur interview, undated; 1 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002091399072)
      - Williams, C. K., undated; 1 (Box 39, Item barcode 39002091399064)
- September 1993 Acquisition, 1960-1991; 2; 52.46; (49 boxes)
  Arranged in no particular order.
  Boxes 79, 83 (audio and video cassettes): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Box 84 (reel-to-reel tapes): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Books, manuscripts, correspondence and other papers relating to Al Poulin and BOA Editions.
  Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 297.
  - Correspondence, circa 1988-1989; 6 (Box 40)
  - Crucifix on wood and velvet mount (Box 40)
  - Evangelatos, C.: correspondence (Box 40)
  - Grant applications (Box 40)
  - F-C course & applications to NEH et al. (Box 40)
  - Unidentified personal papers (Box 40)
  - AMCAP (Box 40)
  - CORA (Box 40)
  - Baudelaire: Paris Spleen (Box 40)
  - Cave Dwellers (Box 40)
  - Unread manuscripts (Box 40)
  - UNE Honorary Degree (Box 40)
  - A. Poulin, Professor of English, Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 40)
  - Letters from Poulin to Alice Poulin, circa 1975-1989; 7 (Box 41)
  - School papers, notes, reading lists, etc., circa 1960; 20 (Box 41)
  - School papers, notes, reading lists, etc., circa 1960-1969; 11 (Box 42)
  - BOA Editions Archive: promotional material, correspondence, manuscripts and proofs, 6 (Box 42)
  - Logan, John: "A Street Named Joy," typescript (copy) (Box 43)
  - Logan, John: "Uncollected Poems," typescript (Box 43)
  - BOA Editions: Rejects, 1990-1991; 6 (Box 43)
  - Printed material, 9 (Box 43)
  - Printed material, 2 (Box 44)
  - BOA Poets (Box 44)
  - Anghelaki-Rooke, Katerina: "Beings and Things On Their Own," correspondence, manuscripts and proofs, 1986; 3 (Box 44)
  - Lee, Li-Young: manuscripts and proofs, 2 (Box 44)
  - Piccione, Anthony: "Seeing It Was So," correspondence, manuscripts and proofs, circa 1986; 6 (Box 44)
  - Tremblay, Bill: "Duhamel," correspondence, manuscripts and proofs, circa 1986; 3 (Box 44)
  - Crosby, William H.: "The Flowers of Evil and Paris Spleen," by Charles Baudelaire, translation; manuscript, proofs, and printed version, 11 (Box 45)
  - Mathieu, Bertrand: "A Season In Hell and Illuminations," by Charles Baudelaire, translation; proofs and printed version, 4 (Box 45)
  - Gardner, Isabella (Box 46)
  - Makuck: Novel (Box 46)
  - Lee, Li-Young: "Furious Versions" (Box 46)
  - Logan: Copyright / books (Box 46)
  - "John Logan: The Collected Poems," proof copy, 4 (Box 46)
  - Friar, Kimon and Myrsiades, Kostas, eds.: "Yannis Ritsos: Selected Poems," bound proof (Box 46)
  - Laux, Dorianne: "How Far You Go?", typescript (Box 46)
  - Boa Editions: rejects, 1989; 4 (Box 46)
  - BOA Editions: checks, receipts, and other financial records, 1987-1988; 45 (Box 47)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, 1988 (Box 47)
  - Friar Kimon: "Takis Varvitsiotis: The Eye in the Mirror" (Box 47)
  - Crow, Mary: "Homecoming" (Box 47)
  - Clifton, Lucille: "Next," boards (Box 47)
  - Poulin, Al: "Anne Hébert: Selected Poems," translation, proofs, 4 (Box 47)
  - Cheimōnas, Giōrgos: manuscripts (Box 48)
  - Mathieu, Bertrand (Box 48)
  - Kizer, Carolyn (Box 48)
  - Unidentified manuscript (Box 48)
  - Schwartz, Delmore: "Shenandoah and Other Verse Plays," proof (Box 48)
  - Crosby, William H.: "The Flowers of Evil and Paris Spleen," by Charles Baudelaire, translation, proofs, 6 (Box 48)
  - Earth, Air, Fire & Water: Poems Selected by Frances McCullough, revised edition, 1989 (Box 48)
  - Moyers: The Power of the Word, promotional material (Box 48)
  - Plutzik: correspondence and manuscripts (Box 49)
  - BOA Authors: correspondence and manuscripts (Box 49)
  - Makuck, Peter: correspondence and manuscripts (Box 49)
  - Hébert, Anne: correspondence and promotional material (Box 49)
  - Di Pasquale, Emanuel: correspondence, manuscripts and proofs (Box 49)
  - Clifton, Lucille: correspondence and proofs (Box 49)
  - Patrick, William B.: "Roxa," boards and spine sampling, 1989; 3 (Box 49)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, 1989; 3 (Box 49)
  - Crow, Mary: "Borders," manuscripts and proofs, 1989 (Box 49)
  - New Worlds of Literature, Jerome Beaty and J. Paul Hunter, eds., 1989 (Box 49)
  - BOA Editions: magazines for review, 3 (Box 49)
  - Anghelaki-Rooke, Katerina: correspondence and manuscripts (Box 50)
  - Clifton, Lucille: "Good Woman," manuscripts and proofs, 2 (Box 50)
  - Friar, Kimon: correspondence (Box 50)
  - Lee, Li-Young: correspondence (Box 50)
  - Logan, John: manuscripts (Box 50)
  - Makuck, Peter: correspondence, manuscripts, and reprints (Box 50)
  - Mathieu, Bertrand: correspondence (Box 50)
  - Plutzik, Hyam: manuscripts, proofs, and promotional material, 3 (Box 50)
  - Simpson, Louis: correspondence, manuscripts, and proofs, 3 (Box 50)
  - Snodgrass, W. D.: correspondence (Box 50)
  - Tremblay, Bill: correspondence (Box 50)
  - BOA Editions: fliers, 1986-1987 (Box 50)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, 1987; 3 (Box 50)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, 1985-1987; 4 (Box 51)
  - Books, 11 (Box 51)
  - Contemporary American Poetry, corrected proofs, correspondence, and manuscripts, circa 1990; 9 (Box 52)
  - "John Logan: The Collected Poems," boards, 9 (Box 53)
  - "Yannis Ritsos: Selected Poems," corrected proofs, 6 (Box 53)
  - "Being Again," worksheets (Box 54)
  - Graywolf Press: correspondence (Box 54)
  - Hébert, Anne: correspondence and manuscripts (Box 54)
  - "In Advent," printed version (Box 54)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 54)
  - "A Momentary Order," typescript and proofs, 4 (Box 54)
  - Worksheets (Box 54)
  - "John Logan: Collected Poems," typescripts and proofs, 4 (Box 55)
  - "Anne Hébert: Selected Poems," correspondence and proofs, 2 (Box 55)
  - Simpson, Louis: correspondence and typescripts (Box 55)
  - Piccione, Anthony: correspondence, 1988 (Box 55)
  - BOA Authors: correspondence, 1988 (Box 55)
  - Di Pasquale, Emanuel: "Genesis," typescript and correspondence, circa 1988; 4 (Box 55)
  - Patrick, William: "Roxa," typescript (Box 55)
  - "Cave Dwellers," typescript and corrected galleys, 1990 (Box 56)
  - "Contemporary American Poetry," drafts, correspondence, permissions, proofs, and printed version, 3 (Box 56)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, circa 1990 (Box 56)
  - Am Here Books catalogs, circa 1991 (Box 56)
  - Books, 7 (Box 56)
  - BOA Editions: assorted promotional material (Box 57)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, circa 1990; 3 (Box 57)
  - Printed material, 4 (Box 57)
  - Poulin, Al: "Anne Hébert: Selected Poems," cover proof (Box 57)
  - Makuck, Peter: "Sunken Lightship," corrected galleys (Box 57)
  - American Poetry Review: mechanicals (Box 57)
  - Correspondence regarding Contemporary American Poetry V, "A Momentary Order", circa 1990; 6 (Box 58)
  - Contemporary American Poetry V, notes and revisions (Box 58)
  - BOA Editions: correspondence and related material, 9 (Box 59)
  - Crosby, William H.: The Flowers of Evil and Paris Spleen, by Charles Baudelaire, translation, typescripts, proofs, and assorted material, 8 (Box 60)
  - Poulin, Al: tenure materials, circa 1976; 49 (Box 61)
  - Brockport College (Box 62)
  - Writers Forum (Box 62)
  - Annual Report, 1982 (Box 62)
  - Poulin, Al: tenure material (Box 62)
  - BOA Editions: 15th Anniversary Gala advertisement flyers (Box 62)
  - Rimbaud (Box 62)
  - Baudelaire, 2 (Box 62)
  - Geraldine Dodge Foundation annual reports, 1986, 1988 (Box 62)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, 1990-1991; 5 (Box 62)
  - Books and other printed material (Box 63)
  - Books and other printed material (Box 64)
  - Correspondence, "Daphne letters, etc.", circa 1990 (Box 64)
  - Readings (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous proposals (Box 64)
  - Correspondence (Box 64)
  - Essays, notes, and interviews (Box 64)
  - Poulin, Al: A Momentary Order, flyers (Box 64)
  - Poulin, Al: "Four Poems," reprints (Box 64)
  - BOA Editions: correspondence and typescripts, 6 (Box 65)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, circa 1991; 2 (Box 65)
  - John Logan: The Collected Fiction, proof (Box 65)
  - Anghelaki-Rook, Katerina: Beings and Things On Their Own, printed version (Box 65)
  - Literature: An Introduction to Reading and Writing, printed version (Box 66)
  - BOA Editions: grant applications, reports, proposals and other documents (Box 66)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, 1988; 3 (Box 66)
  - Yannis Ritsos: Selected Poems, drafts, 5 (Box 66)
  - BOA Editions: correspondence, 4 (Box 66)
  - Taxes, 1984 (Box 67)
  - Graywolf and Houghton-Mifflin correspondence (Box 67)
  - American Poetry Book Club (Box 67)
  - Paul VI UN Visit, 1985 October 5 (Box 67)
  - Contemporary American Poetry, advertising material (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, circa 1986 (Box 67)
  - "Ground Work," uncorrected proofs (Box 67)
  - Louisiana State University: correspondence (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, circa 1986; 2 (Box 67)
  - "Two Conversations with Louis Simpson" (Box 67)
  - Transcript of interview with Michael Harper, 1985 (Box 67)
  - "Migration of Powers," typescript (Box 67)
  - Kayalis, Takis: correspondence and dissertation (Box 67)
  - Correspondence regarding publications and readings (Box 67)
  - Hyam Plutzik: The Collected Poems, proofs, boards, printed version, and advertising material, 10 (Box 68)
  - Clifton, Lucille: Next, typescript and proofs (Box 68)
  - ICLA (Box 69)
  - Publications (Box 69)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, 1984 (Box 69)
  - Poulin, Al: Will and testament, original drafts (Box 69)
  - Taxes, 1982-1983; 3 (Box 69)
  - Correspondence, circa 1985; 3 (Box 69)
  - Calendars (Box 69)
  - Clifton, Lucille: Next and Good Woman, typescripts, drafts and boards, 9 (Box 70)
  - Anne Hébert: Selected Poems, typescript (Box 70)
  - Tremblay, Bill: Duhamel, dust jackets (Box 70)
  - Suskind, Harriet: "In a Different House," typescript (copy) (Box 70)
  - Suskind, Harriet: "To See the Speech of Trees," typescript (copy) (Box 70)
  - Waters, Michael: "The Burden Lifters," typescript (copy) (Box 70)
  - Books and other printed material (Box 71)
  - Hyam Plutzik: Collected Poems, typescripts, blue sheet for dust cover, and index cards, 2 (Box 72)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, circa 1986-1987; 8 (Box 72)
  - Lee, Li-Young: Rose, printed version (Box 72)
  - Shoaf, Diann Blakely: Hurricane Walk, typescript (Box 73)
  - Assorted proofs and typescripts (Box 73)
  - Yannis Ritsos: Selected Poems, bound proof (Box 73)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, circa 1989 (Box 73)
  - Isabella Gardner: The Collected Poems, manuscript and proof, 2 (Box 73)
  - Makuck, Peter: "Backwaters," typescripts, 2 (Box 73)
  - Peseroff, Joyce: "Darwin at the Summer House," typescript (Box 73)
  - BOA Editions: correspondence with authors (Box 73)
  - Gioseffi, Daniela: "Word Wounds, Water Flowers," typescript (Box 73)
  - Ledger (Box 73)
  - Logan, John: Fiction (Box 73)
  - Crow, Mary: Borders, boards (Box 74)
  - Gardner, Isabella: That Was Then and Collected Poems, typescripts and proofs, 3 (Box 74)
  - Logan, John: correspondence regarding estate, Collected Poems typescripts and proof, 3 (Box 74)
  - Patrick, William: Roxa, manuscript (Box 74)
  - Ritsos, Yannis: typescripts and correspondence, 3 (Box 74)
  - Shoaf, Diann Blakely: "Hurricane Walk," typescripts (Box 74)
  - Wallenstein, Barry: Beast Is a Wind With Brown Fire, printed version (Box 74)
  - BOA Editions: correspondence (Box 75)
  - BOA Editions: subsidiary rights (Box 75)
  - NYSCA, 1983-1984 (Box 75)
  - Makuck, Peter: "The Sunken Lightship," proofs (Box 75)
  - "People Live Here," corrected pages (Box 75)
  - Spine and cover stamps (Box 75)
  - Laux, Dorianne: Awake, proof (Box 75)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, circa 1990; 3 (Box 75)
  - Books (Box 75)
  - BOA Editions: fund-raising letters (Box 76)
  - BOA Editions: check stubs (Box 76)
  - Crow, Mary: typescripts (Box 76)
  - Patrick, William: Roxa, typescripts, proofs, printed version, 7 (Box 76)
  - Ritsos, Yannis: typescripts, correspondence, proofs, 4 (Box 76)
  - John XXIII newspapers (Box 77)
  - Ledger (Box 77)
  - Tremblay, Bill: Duhamel, typescript and proof, 2 (Box 77)
  - Anghelaki-Rooke, Katerina: Beings and Things On Their Own, typescripts (Box 77)
  - Contemporary American Poetry, proof pages (Box 77)
  - Poulin, Al: "Glass Snake," postcards (Box 77)
  - Plutzik, Hyam: typescripts (Box 77)
  - Ramsey, Jerold: letters and material relating to Hyam Plutzik (Box 77)
  - BOA Editions: Item correspondence, circa 1988; 2 (Box 77)
  - BOA Editions: correspondence, circa 1981 (Box 77)
  - Phillips, Robert: typescript (copy) (Box 77)
  - Marvin, David: typescripts (Box 77)
  - Correspondence, circa 1988 (Box 77)
  - Patrick, William: Roxa, proofs (Box 77)
  - BOA Editions: Hellenic-American Foundation (Box 77)
  - Lee, Li-Young: Rose, typescript, boards, printed version, 3 (Box 77)
  - BOA Editions: financial, 1983 (Box 77)
  - BOA Editions: check stubs, 1983-1985 (Box 78)
  - BOA Editions: receipts, 1984-1985; 3 (Box 78)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, 4 (Box 78)
  - BOA Editions: job applications, 2 (Box 78)
  - Costanzo, Gerald: Nobody Lives on Arthur Godfrey Boulevard, printed version (copy) (Box 78)
  - Schwartz, Delmore: Shenandoah and other Verse Plays, printed version (copy) (Box 78)
  - Shoaf, Diann Blakely: Hurricane Walk, boards (Box 78)
  - Tremblay, William: "Jane Rise," typescript, 1992 (Box 78)
  - Correspondence (Box 78)
  - Rimbaud, Arthur: A Season In Hell and Illuminations, translated by Bertrand Mathieu, printed version and proof, 2 (Box 79)
  - Schwartz, Delmore: Shenandoah and Other Verse Plays, proof (Box 79)
  - BOA Editions: correspondence, circa 1992; 5 (Box 79)
  - "Diana's Hair Ego: Aids Info Up Front," "Silent Echoes," "Her Giveaway: A Spiritual Journey with AIDS", undated; YCALMSS635_0001; 1; 00:59:21 (Box 133)
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Contact Access Services for further information.
  - Books (Box 79)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, 1989-1992; 4 (Box 80)
  - BOA Editions: promotional posters (Box 80)
  - Logan, John: John Logan: The Collected Fiction, bound proof (Box 80)
  - Clifton, Lucille: Quilting, proof (Box 80)
  - Magazines, 3 (Box 80)
  - Collection inventory (Box 80)
  - Lee, Li-Young: promotional material (Box 80)
  - Clifton, Lucille: promotional material (Box 80)
  - Books (Box 80)
  - Logan, John: John Logan: The Collected Fiction, typescripts and proofs, 4 (Box 81)
  - Clifton, Lucille: Quilting, typescripts and proofs, 6 (Box 81)
  - Mathieu, Bertrand: correspondence, 2 (Box 81)
  - BOA Editions: rejects, circa 1991; 7 (Box 81)